<resources xmlns:xliff="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto">
    <string name="app_name">Norfolk Touring</string>

    <!--Location Category Labels-->
    <string name="parks_category_label">Parks</string>
    <string name="museums_category_label">Museums</string>
    <string name="military_category_label">Military</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category_label">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="others_category_label">Other</string>

    <!--Location Strings-->
    <string name="location_open">Open Now</string>
    <string name="location_closed">Closed</string>

    <!--Military Descriptions-->

    <!--Nauticus-->
    <string name="military_nauticus_desc">
        NAUTICUS inspires and educates with engaging &amp; interactive experiences that celebrate our
        connections with today\'s maritime world. Nauticus is a contemporary museum that uses the
        natural setting of Norfolk\'s harbor to showcase global maritime commerce and the world\'s
        largest Navy.
    </string>
    <!--Nauticus Features-->
    <string name="military_nauticus_uss_wisconsin">
        Berthed at Nauticus, the Battleship Wisconsin is one of the largest and last battleships
        ever built by the U.S. Navy. Explore its deck through a self-guided tour or, with an
        additional charge, our guided Topside Tour that will take you back in time to experience
        this majestic ship that earned five battle stars during WW II.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_hampton_roads_naval_museum">
        The Hampton Roads Naval Museum is an accredited museum operated by the United States Navy
        that celebrates the over 240 year history of the fleet in the Hampton Roads region of
        Virginia. We are located on the second floor of Nauticus in beautiful downtown
        Norfolk, Virginia.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_power_of_the_sea_galleries">
        The Power of the Sea Galleries encompass the entire 3rd floor event area of Nauticus,
        including the Living Sea Landing, the Wisconsin Vista, and the Living Sea Theater.
        Maximum seated capacity of 350.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_wisconsin_vista">
        In this area you can enjoy the breathtaking view of the Battleship Wisconsin through large
        picture windows. This area also includes a variety of computer interactives.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_living_sea_landing">
        The Living Sea Landing features Horseshoe Crab Cove, a simulated tide pool where your
        guests can interact with many of the Chesapeake Bay marine life. It is also home to the
        Shark Experience, and interactive shark tank filled with a variety of friendly sharks.
        The area accommodates 110 seated guests or 250 standing.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_living_sea_theater">
        With seating for up to 350 people, this location is ideal
        for presentations, performances and award ceremonies. It features a large format screen.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_lighthouse_portico">
        The Lighthouse Portico is Nauticus’s expansive front entrance
        deck, with access to the waterfront.  Cool breezes off the river
        make this a delightful area to entertain.
    </string>
    <string name="military_nauticus_elizabeth_river_pavilion">
        This outdoor covered event area offers up beautiful views of
        the Elizabeth River, as well as protection from inclement
        weather.  With a seated capacity of 550 and a standing
        capacity of 900, it is the largest event area on the
        Nauticus grounds. Add in the parking lot and capacity
        increases to 1200 standing.
    </string>

    <!--MacArthur Memorial-->
    <string name="military_macarthur_memorial_desc">
        The MacArthur Memorial is a museum and research center dedicated to preserving and
        presenting the story of the life of General of the Army Douglas MacArthur. The Memorial
        also pays tribute to the millions of men and women who served with General MacArthur
        in World War I, World War II, and the Korean War.
    </string>

    <!--Museums Descriptions-->

    <!--Chrysler Museum of Art-->
    <string name="museum_chrysler_museum_desc">
        The Chrysler Museum of Art is a rare gem, with small but inspirational collections of art
        and antiquities, all well laid out in a lovely building, newly renovated in 2014. This free
        museum has one of the country\'s leading glass collections. Even visitors who are not
        interested in art cannot help but be impressed by the beauty and creativity found in this
        collection. In addition, the museum features European and American painting and sculpture,
        modern art, contemporary art, photography, decorative arts, and ancient art. From Henri
        Matisse to Andy Warhol, the museum\'s permanent collection offers a bit of everything, and
        temporary exhibitions ensure return visits are in order.
        \n
        \nNext door to the main museum is the Chrysler Museum Glass Studio, where artists come to
        work at their craft, and guests can see demonstrations in glass blowing.
        Classes and workshops are also available.
    </string>

    <!--Hampton Roads Naval Museum-->
    <string name="museum_hampton_roads_naval_museum_desc">
        @string/military_nauticus_hampton_roads_naval_museum
    </string>

    <!--Hermitage Museum & Gardens-->
    <string name="museum_hermitage_museum_and_gardens_desc">
        Historic home and picturesque gardens offering a fine art collection,
        professional program and classes.
    </string>

    <!--Other Descriptions-->

    <!--Norfolk Botanical Garden-->
    <string name="other_norfolk_botanical_garden_desc">
        The Norfolk Botanical Garden is a botanical garden with an arboretum located at 6700
        Azalea Garden Road, Norfolk, Virginia.
    </string>

    <!--The Virginia Zoo-->
    <string name="other_virginia_zoo_desc">
        The Virginia Zoological Park is a 53-acre zoo
        located adjacent to Lafayette Park in Norfolk, Virginia, United States.
        The zoo opened in 1900, and was accredited by the Association of Zoos and Aquariums in 1987.
    </string>

    <!--American Rover-->
    <string name="other_american_rover_desc">
        Docked in downtown Norfolk, not far from Nauticus, is the tall ship, American Rover.
        This three-masted schooner offers sailing cruises on the Elizabeth River and Hampton Roads
        Harbor, with fantastic views of the city and surroundings. These narrated cruises last an
        hour and a half to two hours and run from April to October. Guests can help with the sailing
        if they want a little hands-on experience, or simply enjoy the ride. Snacks and beverages
        are sold on the ship, but guests are also welcome to bring their own food on with them if
        they choose. Cruises can be booked 30 days in advance, but it is often possible to get
        tickets at the last minute. Afternoon and sunset cruises are available, and occasionally
        special sailings are scheduled, including night cruises.
    </string>

    <!--Parks Descriptions-->

    <!--Town Point Park-->
    <string name="parks_town_point_park_desc">
        Located in the heart of downtown Norfolk, Town Point Park provides seven acres of peaceful
        green space along the Elizabeth River. Town Point Park is Norfolk\'s premier waterfront
        entertainment venue and serves as a destination for signature festivals,
        cultural and educational events.
    </string>

    <!--Ocean View Beach Park-->
    <string name="parks_ocean_view_beach_park_desc">
        This unique 6.5-acre beach park, is considered the jewel of Ocean View.
        The park has a large band shell for presentations and dancing, a beach with lifeguards
        in the summer, a boardwalk, beach handicap access ramp, and lots of open green space.
    </string>

    <!--Restaurants Descriptions-->

    <!--Franco's-->
    <string name="restaurants_francos_desc">
        Comfy, time-tested option serving pizza, pasta and other Italian comfort food,
        plus beer and wine.
    </string>

    <!--Azalea Inn & Time Out Sports Bar-->
    <string name="restaurants_azalea_inn_desc">
        Italian and Greek dishes meet pizza and burgers in a casual, paneled tavern with
        sports photos and TVs.
    </string>

    <!--Paradise Pizzera-->
    <string name="restaurants_paradise_pizzera_desc">
        Delivery, Dine In, Pick Up and Catering Breakfast, Pizza, Stromboli, Calzones, Salads,
        Wings, Pasta, Dinners, Desserts, Catering and more for entire Family.
    </string>

    <!--Regino's-->
    <string name="restaurants_reginos_desc">
        Understated joint dishing up classic pizzas, hearty pasta dishes and
        other Italian comfort foods.
    </string>

    <!--Doumars-->
    <string name="restaurants_doumars_desc">
        Landmark stop since 1904 serving BBQ, burgers, dogs and sandwiches
        plus soda fountain favorites.
    </string>

    <!--Handsome Biscuit-->
    <string name="restaurants_handsome_biscuit_desc">
        Tiny breakfast and lunch joint serving a variety of sweet-potato biscuit sandwiches,
        sides and desserts.
    </string>

    <!-- Detail View -->

    <!--Detail View Section Headers-->
    <string name="detail_view_name_header_text">Name:</string>
    <string name="detail_view_address_header_text">Address:</string>
    <string name="detail_view_contact_info_header_text">Contact Info:</string>
    <string name="detail_view_features_header_text">Features:</string>
    <string name="detail_view_description_header_text">Full Description:</string>

    <!--Detail View Rating-->
    <string name="detail_view_rating_header_text">Rating:</string>

    <!--Detail View Hours of Operation-->
    <string name="location_hours_header">Hours:</string>
    <string name="sunday_header">Sun</string>
    <string name="monday_header">Mon</string>
    <string name="tuesday_header">Tues</string>
    <string name="wednesday_header">Wed</string>
    <string name="thursday_header">Thur</string>
    <string name="friday_header">Fri</string>
    <string name="saturday_header">Sat</string>

    <!--Detail View Website-->
    <string name="detail_view_website_header_text">Website:</string>

    <!--Detail View Google Images-->
    <string name="google_image_attribution">Image attributed to %s</string>
    <string name="location_detail_resource_image_label_text">Chosen Images</string>
    <string name="location_detail_google_image_label_text">Images from Google</string>

    <!--Distances-->

    <string name="location_distance_main_view">%d meters away</string>
    <string name="location_distance_detail_view">%d meters away</string>
    <string name="detail_view_distance_header_text">Distance:</string>

    <!--Introduction Fragment-->

    <string name="introductory_header_text">Welcome to Norfolk, Virginia!</string>
    <string name="introductory_text">
        This application shows various locations of interest in Norfolk, Virgina.
        \n
        \nSwipe from the left side of the screen to open a drawer from which you may select various
        categories of locations of interest: parks, museums, military locations, restaurants,
        and other locations.
    </string>
    <!-- Media Playback -->
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="introductory_video_media_notification_title">NorfolkTouring YouTube player controls</string>
    <string name="introductory_video_media_notification_text">Click the icons to control the player</string>

    <!-- Google Maps Icons -->

    <!--Google Maps Icon Text-->
    <string name="location_resource_google_maps_text">Google Maps View</string>
    <!--Google Maps Route Planning Icon Text-->
    <string name="location_resource_google_maps_route_plan_text">Plan Route</string>

    <!-- Permissions and Services-->

    <!-- LocationService -->
    <string name="LocationServiceDescription">
        Acquires location data for the NorfolkTouring app.
    </string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">
        NorfolkTouring needs to access this device\'s location
        to determine distance from touring locations.
    </string>

    <!--Menus-->

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--SharedPreferences-->

    <!-- NOTE: All keys should have translatable="false" to avoid unneeded localization. -->
    <string name="pref_enable_wifi_cell_data_usage_key" translatable="false">enable_wifi_cell_data_usage</string>
    <string name="pref_enable_wifi_cell_data_usage_summary_off">Disabled</string>
    <string name="pref_enable_wifi_cell_data_usage_summary_on">Enabled</string>
    <string name="pref_enable_wifi_cell_data_usage_title">Enable WiFi/Cell Data Usage</string>

    <!--Nearest Location Updates-->

    <string name="nearest_location_notification_title">
        Nearest location is <xliff:g id="name">%s</xliff:g>
    </string>
    <string name="nearest_location_notification_body">
        It is <xliff:g id="name">%d</xliff:g> meters away.
    </string>

    <!--Miscellaneous-->

    <string name="not_available">N/A</string>
    <string name="open_status_unavailable">Open Status Uncertain</string>

</resources>
